{
    "word parameters": {
        "excluded": [
            "abuse",
            "abused",
            "abusing",
            "assault",
            "assaulted",
            "assaulting",
            "rape",
            "raped",
            "raping",
            "molest",
            "molested",
            "molesting",
            "suicide",
            "suicidal",
            "kill",
            "killer",
            "killing",
            "update",
            "edit"
        ],
        "minimum length question": "20",
        "maximum length question": "500",
        "minimum length answer": "20",
        "maximum length answer": "400"
    },
    "before": {
        "mean length of answer": "87.64016736401673",
        "mean length of question": "232.81171548117155",
        "std question": "179.39918938348197",
        "std_answer": "80.68739861051822",
        "longest answer": "804",
        "longest question": "1219",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "12",
        "number of items": "239"
    },
    "after": {
        "mean length of answer": "87.32402234636872",
        "mean length of question": "222.9608938547486",
        "std question": "167.51490763739585",
        "std_answer": "71.95425326269239",
        "longest answer": "410",
        "longest question": "1004",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "12",
        "number of items": "179"
    }
}